Guide to the William Henry Jackson Photographs, 1869-1874 RL.00625
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Album: Photographic Views Of the Yellow Stone National Park Series, 1871-1872, 1 box
  - "272 Camp on the Yellowstone Lake, Yellowstone Series 1871" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P39)
  - "274 Yellowstone Lake, North West Arm, Yellowstone Series 1871" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P40)
  - "275 Hot Spring Cone, in Yellowstone Lake, Hot Springs Series" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P41)
  - "276 Basin of Hot Springs, on Yellowstone Lake, Hot Springs Series" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P42)
  - "279 Yellowstone Lake, Birds Eye View From South East Arm, Yellowstone Series 1871" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P43)
  - "281 Yellowstone Lake, Birds Eye View From South East Arm, Yellowstone Series 1871" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P44)
  - "282 Yellowstone Lake, Birds Eye View From South East Arm, Yellowstone Series 1871" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P45)
  - "286 Yellowstone Lake, South East Arm, Yellowstone Series 1871" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P46)
  - "287 Yellowstone Lake, South East Arm, Yellowstone Series 1871" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P47)
  - "288 Earthquake Camp, East Side Yellowstone Lake, Yellowstone Series 1871" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P48)
    copy negative available: WHJ.Album.N48
  - "294 Castle Geyser, Fire Hole Basin, Hot Spring Series" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P49)
  - "295 Castle Geyser and Hot Spring, Fire Hole Basin, Hot Spring Series " (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P50)
  - "296 Giant Geyser, Fire Hole Basin, Hot Spring Series" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P51)
  - "297 Grotto Geyser, Fire Hole Basin, Hot Spring Series" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P52)
  - "298 Grotto Geyser, Fire Hole Basin, Hot Spring Series" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P53)
  - "439 Crater of Old Faithful, 1872 Series" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P54)
  - "433 Crater of Architectural Geyser, Lower Fire Hole Basin, 1872 Series" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P55)
  - "444 Crater of Grand Geyser, 1872 Series" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P56)
  - "442 The Bee Hive, 1872 Series" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P57)
  - "434 Great Hot Springs Between Upper and Lower Basins, 1872 Series" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P58)
  - "446 Distant View of the Castle in Eruption, 1872 Series" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P59)
  - "443 The Giantess, 1872 Series" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P60)
  - "435 Upper Fire Hole, Looking Up, 1872 Series" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P61)
  - "307 Extinct Hot Springs, East Fork of the Yellowstone, Hot Spring Series" (Box WHJ7, Print WHJ.Album.P62)